{"data":[{"question":"Public transport is rarely adapted to the needs of ______.","a":"disables","b":"the disables","c":"the disable people","d":"the disabled","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+ \"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This is the ______.","a":"entrance door","b":"entrance's door","c":"door's entrance","d":"door entrance","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The ______ don't like learning languages.","a":"English","b":"English people","c":"people English","d":"Englishmen","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+\"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Let's buy those ______.","a":"wine glasses","b":"glasses wine","c":"wine's glasses","d":"glasses' wine","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Look at those ______.","a":"house wooden","b":"wood houses","c":"houses wood","d":"wooden houses","answer":"4","explain":"\n-Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun\n+ Structure: Adj + Noun\n+ wood (n) -> wooden (adj)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This is a beautiful ______.","a":"chair garden","b":"garden chair","c":"chair's garden","d":"garden's chair","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a ______ at one side of the road.","a":"stone's wall","b":"wall's stone","c":"stone wall","d":"wall stone","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"A woman who drives a car is called a ______.","a":"woman driver","b":"driver woman","c":"driver's woman","d":"woman's driver","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Here is your ______.","a":"morning's tea","b":"tea morning","c":"tea's morning","d":"morning tea","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He worked as a ______.","a":"night watchman","b":"watch night","c":"night watch","d":"watching night","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}